# **Andrey Chuchalov**

## Full-Stack Developer

Address: Tel Aviv District, Israel. Mobile: +972 55-770-53-19 andy.tchu@gmail.com https://github.com/andy-tchu/https://www.linkedin.com/in/andrey-chuchalov-982536282/

## **Summary:**

With over 20 years in IT, I've excelled as a developer, system analyst, and project manager, delivering successful enterprise projects for major companies. I specialize in collaborative cross-functional teamwork, ensuring projects meet deadlines and quality benchmarks. Now build my career as a full-stack developer.

#### Actual technical skills:

- Python, NodeJS;
- SQL (Oracle, PostgreSQL);
- NoSQL (MongoDB);

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript;
- Git, Jira, Confluence;
- Windows, Linux.

**Soft skills:** System analysis, project management, problem-solving, and team collaboration.

## **Professional experience:**

## Full-Stack Developer, Freelance, Israel (2023-current time)

Designing and implementing scalable, efficient, and robust web applications (landings, internet stores, and so on) for clients across various industries. My expertise spans across full-stack development with a focus on modern web technologies such as NodeJS, Python, TypeScript, Angular, and MongoDB.

## Senior System Analyst, Rostelecom, Moscow (2017-2023)

Worked as a senior system analyst and project manager and took a key part in the development of internal products for B2O and B2B segments. Conducted system analytics, database design, and API specification and development. Also authored SQL queries for extracting data from diverse systems, normalizing data, and preparing aggregated data for reports and designed and developed APIs for integration with external systems. Assumed the role of project manager on select projects.

## IT Consultant, Social Insurance Fund of Russian Federation, Moscow (2011 - 2017)

Contributed as a system analyst, crafting and reviewing project documentation, stepped into the role of a system architect to design high-level architecture, and assumed project management responsibilities, liaising with subcontractors for the successful development and rollup of projects working around the country.

#### Software Developer, UralSoftProject, Izhevsk, Russia (2007 – 2011)

I participated as a C#, SQL, PL\SQL developer in the development of the Invest Planning System for the Oil Company Rosneft.

#### Software Developer, Aspec-Nefteproduct, Izhevsk, Russia (1999 - 2007)

I developed and maintained report systems using Delphi and Sybase within the software framework for the gas station network "IT-Oil." Additionally, I served as a Database Administrator (DBA) for these systems, managing Oracle and Sybase databases.

#### **Education:**

1994 - 1999 Master's degree, Computer Programming, Izhevsk State Technical University

#### Language:

Russian – native, English – professional working, Hebrew – elementary.